You know how I came up with the idea
for the Triple-X program?
Skateboards and swimming pools.
Skateboards used to be
stuck on the ground.
Adolescent transportation.
Then 1977 happens.
Big drought hits Southern California.
Got so bad, rich suburbanites couldn't
afford to fill their swimming pools.
That's when the light clicked on.
Some kid figured out
he could skate those empty pools
and get some real nasty air.
Dogtown and Z-Boys. You ever seen it?
It's a movie.
Doesn't matter.
Anyhow, our hero starts
doing things on a board
that no one's ever seen before.
Things the world thought
were impossible.
Now, that kid needed that drought.
The world needed those empty pools.
That's why Triple-X.
Do you feel safer today
than you felt yesterday?
I know I don't.
The biggest,
most expensive military in the world,
and we're still scared of shoe
and tighty-whitey bombs at the airport.
Why is that?
Because soldiers are built to
take orders and fight wars.
But we, my friend, are not at war.
We are at peril.
That's why Triple-X.
What's the matter? You on a diet?
You ain't hungry?
It's seven-thirty in the morning.
So? It's lunch or dinnertime
somewhere in the world.
Come on, eat up!
You know who does feel safe?
The men in charge. The world beaters.
The top-shelf, par excellence ayatollahs
with all the "dollahs."
And that's because
those righteous bastards,
somewhere along the way,
made a deal with the devil.
They traded liberty for safety. And us,
we the people,
ended up losing both.
That's why Triple-X.
While everybody else
is stuck on the ground,
we're doing shit on the board
nobody's ever even seen before.
Well, that's my pitch.
I always was a better spy
than a salesman.
So, what do you say?
I'm no hero.
I'm no hero. I'm just a footballer.
My bad.
So, I'll leave you be, then.
Who said there's no such thing
as a free meal?
Down on the ground, now!
Give me the money!
Don't move! Hurry up!
Goal!
And you say you're no hero.
I got to call bullshit on that!
You're exactly the kind of hero
the world needs.
At the end of the day,
it comes down to the same question
I've been asking my wife
every Friday night for the last 20 years.
Do you want some of this?
Or are you just gonna...
Access granted.
Okay, you may sit.
Gentlemen,
this is the device that crashed
the satellite and killed Gibbons.
Nerds in the lab
have coined it "Pandora's Box."
My team backtracked
the satellite's last signal input to Miami.
Some asshole living the high life
at the Ritz-Carlton penthouse
thought he could hold the world ransom.
Three flashbangs, two bullets,
and one body bag later,
we took custody of the device.
We must have
over 100 redundancies in place
to prevent some punk with a laptop
from hijacking satellites.
And Pandora's Box
can bypass all of them.
With the push of a button,
it can eavesdrop on
secure communications,
corrupt military software,
transmit false intelligence, or
crash a satellite out of the sky
like a goddamn tactical warhead.
One of you is behind this.
And I am not leaving here
until I find out who.
You fight me with a book?
Here you go, brother. Chapter one!
Page one!
Shit happens.
You're late!
Just in time, boss.
They bust in here,
step on our throats,
and take the one device
that can cause a global power shift.
So, how do we get it back?
These assholes just took out
the best of the best
like it was Sunday brunch.
We need someone
who can move like them, fight like them.
who can walk into a tornado,
and come out the other side
like it was a damn gentle breeze.
You know someone like that?
No.
But Gibbons did.
- What you doing?
- That's loco, chico!
Xander!
Whoo!
Hey friend...
...give me a second.
And here we go, we are underway!
I knew you would do it, Xander.
You brought the world to us.
The world is big,
but always fits in your heart.
Take it with you always.
Go, go, go.
Of course, Xander Cage
can't pay the satellite company,
just like a regular guy.
What?
And line the pockets of some
boardroom billionaires?
You know,
these days,
a regular guy can't afford to be regular.
Let's go.
World getting smaller?
I know the feeling.
Running from your problems
never works out.
You need a new plan.
I need a new map.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Oh, boy.
Here we go again.
Down! Get down! Don't move, asshole!
On your knees now, you son of a bitch!
Okay, okay. I want to comply.
I really wanna comply.
But you're confusing me.
"Don't move, you asshole."
"On your knees, you son of a bitch."
Which is it?
You have three seconds to comply!
You're not good at this.
One!
Two!
Okay!
Come on out, Frankenstein!
Gibbons! Gibbons?
Olly-olly-oxen-free.
Wow.
You really do look different, Gibbons.
Did you lose weight?
Augustus always had such, well,
not exactly nice things to say about you.
When did you realize it was all fake?
You mean the clown show?
You had a guy over there
wearing $1,000 Beats
when you can buy the knockoff
for half the price.
Or the lady that was running
to catch a bus
that doesn't leave for two hours.
Or the security guard over there
buying a soda with foreign currency?
Oh, you know what the kicker was?
Clarence from It's a Wonderful Life.
The nice old man that you had sit down
next to me with the bag of bombs?
Just happened to know I spoke English.
Go figure.
The bullets could've been real.
Then the body armor
would've been real.
I don't know you, but...
I don't like to be tested.
Gibbons never believed you were dead!
Never stopped looking for you.
Hell of a friend.
Yeah, well, the joke's on him.
'Cause we were never friends.
Oh, trust me, he's not laughing.
Nor will he ever again, for that matter.
I've never seen anything like it.
This group is lethal,
and they don't care
who or what gets in their way.
I was hoping you'd be interested
in headlining the next fight card.
Seventy feet across,
90 feet down.
Three inches of security glass?
No rope. No line. No chute.
I bet they had a blast.
We ran facial IDs on
every database in the world.
Nothing. Not even a match
on a speeding ticket.
They're ghosts, in a day and age where
that kind of thing is almost impossible.
Okay,
you get that I don't work for suits.
What makes you think
I'm gonna want to ruin all their fun?
Well, if you won't do it for me,
do it for Gibbons.
Your country needs you, Mr. Cage.
The Triple-X program needs you.
It's time to be a patriot.
By whose definition?
The last time I was patriotic,
I got three strikes.
And there was only one man
who believed in the underdog.
Patriotism is dead.
There's only rebels and tyrants now.
So, which are you?
I'm Triple-X.
Well, welcome back, Triple-X.
Uh, where are you going?
- London.
- Why? What's in London?
A ghost hunter.
And possibly my fur coat.
I'd forgotten how beautiful
the view is up here.
Oh, I, uh, see you found your coat.
Well, you promised
to take care of it for me.
And I did.
So, I'm looking for someone.
Since when have we had
a business relationship?
I get caught even touching a computer,
my ass goes away for 20.
Name your price.
You know I'm good for it.
Information like this
doesn't have a price.
Ainsley,
everything has a price.
Now, if you don't think
you can pull it off,
if you lost your edge,
just tell me and I'll understand.
You wanna know what it is, Cage?
What?
I used to think you were the man.
But now,
I don't know, maybe I feel
like you're just working for him.
Come on.
Nobody knows I'm here.
And you know how I am
about keeping secrets.
So you say, but Interpol's
got these new listening bugs.
They're practically invisible.
Real MI6 kind of shit.
Disappear on your skin,
under your arms,
tied around your balls
like a Christmas bow.
Unwrap me, then.
You know, studies have proven that
sexual consummation irrevocably ruins
nine out of 10 relationships.
Lucky for me, you love to gamble.
Of course...
...not.
My friends, on the other hand,
adore stiff odds.
Stiff odds?
Hmm.
The things I do for my country.
Like finding needles
in a stack of needles.
Even though you're shackled
by the Queen,
you're still the best in the world.
Thank you.
Do yourself a favor. Burn this.
The whispers I hear,
these ghosts of yours
are the real kind of trouble.
They've got training,
they've got funding,
and they've got no problem running over
anyone who gets in their way.
Okay, so, you're worried
that I might get hurt?
I'm worried you might get dead.
You know,
I'm touched that you can imagine
a world without me in it.
It'll be a little less fun.
That's all I'm saying.
Your ghosts are hanging out
in the Philippines.
Figures they'd go to the Pacific.
Some jungle rave that's off the grid.
How the hell did you find it so quickly?
Undercover work.
Where is it?
What did you do with Pandora's Box?
It's in a safe place.
That wasn't a part of the plan.
After all these years,
you're still shocked when I improvise?
No. But the mission was to destroy it.
Turns out there's a new mission.
I'm not gonna destroy the one thing
I can use to get what we want.
The whole world
is looking for us, Xiang.
Let them come!
You worry about pawn sacrifice.
I got my eye on the king.
That's the problem.
You forgot the queen.
After your success
taking down Anarchy 99,
Gibbons was handed a blank check.
Which is the long way of saying
he got you a new ride.
World went and got an upgrade
since you died, Cage.
Onboard drones,
anti-air countermeasures,
and fuel tanks big enough
to circumnavigate the globe three times
without ever landing.
You can check your coat.
I promise you,
no one would dare steal it.
I can't guarantee
it won't walk off on its own.
Wheels up in 10, boys!
Which means
you're already seven minutes behind.
Is she always this much fun,
or just on special occasions?
Wow.
No wonder our country's
in debt trillions of dollars.
Do you really need all these gadgets
to get the bad guys?
Oh, we don't need any of it.
But it makes the catching
a hell of a lot more fun.
Hmm.
Xander Cage. Holy shit!
Live and in concert, one night only.
This is crazy!
I was at Coachella and
Guns N' Roses got back together,
but this is way cooler.
Well, I wasn't actually there, but I, like,
heard about it, you know?
I'm still talking. Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, it's like a bad habit.
I get started and then I can't stop
and then I can't...
Breathe.
Take your time.
I know mouth-to-mouth if necessary.
Wow.
Wow!
Are you kidding me with those guns?
You're like the frickin' Terminator!
And I'm not talking
about the first Terminator,
but the second Terminator
that goes back
to kill the first Terminator.
It was the liquidy metal guy.
Agent Clearidge
worked closely with Gibbons.
She'll handle support for the operation.
And I bet a guy like you
needs a lot of support.
What are you? Like 220? 230?
Be honest.
250 is the hard max for my swing.
- Oh, come on.
- I'm kidding.
It's not like I have a safe word,
or anything.
It's "kumquat."
Never really think about it.
Kumquat.
What about you?
No. "Safe" isn't in my vocabulary.
Touché. You are Xander Cage.
Anything you need,
Becky can source it within the hour.
Except for
any sort of illegal drugs.
Those, I'll have within 15 minutes.
Kidding.
But if you need a fifty of Purple Urkle,
I am not the girl to ask.
Okay, Cage, follow me.
I'll introduce you to your ground team.
- Thank you, Becky.
- Of course.
Kumquat.
Hey, here comes the Red Bull
freak show.
Xander Cage,
I want you to meet Paul...
Donovan.
Captain Paul Donovan.
I know you. I saw you on TV!
The President gave him a medal.
That must have been pretty cool, right?
You guys must have
some seriously cool stories to tell.
Must've seen a lot.
I wonder,
how many of you have ever pulled
a freestyle triple backflip
on a BMX bike before? All of you?
No. We don't play on bikes.
Oh, you don't play on bikes.
Any of you ever carve an R4
on a snowboard
while an avalanche is on your booty?
We're soldiers, hotshot. Not slackers.
Okay, but you all
have HALO jumped
over Eastern Europe
using a standard-issue
armor deployment parachute system.
Am I right?
No. We're not all jacked up on
Mountain Dew and Red Bull,
you asshole.
Where'd you find this guy?
Well, there's a first time for everything.
What did you just do?
I can't believe this shit.
I'm not gonna have clowns
watch my back.
I know I'm gonna regret asking you this,
but who would you trust?
You know, no one has this number.
So, what are you up to these days?
Me? I'm evening the odds.
Move in, move in! Show me your hands!
Get on the car, now!
It was like that when I got here.
Nobody gets in unless you're an
X-Game participant! You hear me?
That guy got through.
Hey, get back here!
Wassup, Nyjah?
Lightningbolt and Burrito.
Chad, wassup, bro?
Roberta. I'll see you later.
Show him the love!
Give it up for The Hood!
The good, the bad, the extreme,
and the completely insane.
Now, this is a team I can work with.
I'll make this easy for you.
These four assholes, very bad guys.
Pandora's Box, very bad thing.
We'll land in Manila
and you will requisition
your own transportation to the island.
Yo, why don't we just nuke this bitch
from orbit and call it a day?
Pandora's Box is one of a kind.
It needs to be recovered intact.
Why? What's it do?
- Brainwave scrambler?
- It killed Gibbons.
All you need to know.
The rest is classified.
Brainwave scrambler.
You smell that?
Smells like the same shit
in a different suit.
You think a dog knows
how to work a Frisbee?
Master says, "Fetch,"
and the bitch listens.
You would look so sexy
with a Frisbee in that mouth.
Oh, sweetheart,
this is not a game.
You are all my soldiers now.
I'm not a soldier, I'm a baller.
Do we look like soldiers?
Oh, hell, no.
I dropped your soldiers
over Eastern Europe.
So, why did you leave Lassie behind?
This is my operation!
You will listen to me.
Meeting's over.
Well, other than that, Mrs. Lincoln,
how was the play?
Oh, hey, that's super-cinch body armor.
You've got to tighten the strap...
...over here.
I got this.
What are you, my handler?
I'm whatever you need.
I can handle anything.
And I've got a tight grip.
And just so you know,
I am not a field agent.
I do not go out in the field. Ever.
Now, that's where all the fun is.
Yeah, fun scares me.
People scare me. Guns scare me.
People with guns really scare me.
And if I'm scared, I can't do my job.
And if I can't do my job, then people die.
And if people die,
then who am I tech-supporting?
Literally no one.
But I will make sure to keep you safe.
It ain't easy to keep me safe.
Whoa.
Yeah, these bad boys
are my favorite, too.
They're called exo-gloves.
DARPA's new ground combat initiative.
Pneumatic pistons drive the gears,
quadruple the speed
and power of your punches.
Uh, uh-uh-uh...
Nope, nope.
This is a multistage signal disruptor.
It's very, very breakable.
Can you tell me the real reason
behind the crash of
Pan Am Flight 103 over Lockerbie?
Yes.
Ah. You're one of them, aren't you?
Easy there, Rocky.
I wasn't kidding when I said
there's enough force in these bad boys
to probably punch a hole
through the fricking plane.
Keep screwing around.
What could possibly go wrong?
- That is my style, though.
- Yeah, good. Glad to hear it.
Oh, you know, actually,
I would rather if you didn't...
Oh.
That's refreshing.
You actually know
what you're doing down there.
Yeah. That's what she said.
Wow.
Let them pass!
You need something, man?
Well, I heard this is a perfect place
to disappear for a few days
for my crew, no questions asked.
Mi casa es su casa, if the price is right.
Perfect. Tennyson!
You're gonna like this.
I just happen to have the best hardware
in the South Pacific.
30% off the top
gets you our finest hospitality package.
30% off the top?
Do I get the girls for a weekend
and two coconuts?
10%.
10%?
You must've been aiming
at the other lawless,
uncharted island down the block.
Happens all the time.
Here's what you do.
You turn around, go get your boat.
You can kiss my ass.
Okay, hang on.
What do you think?
You talked me into it!
18%!
You think this is a flea market?
You think we're in the hood
selling TVs and fake watches,
or something like that?
What's wrong with you, man?
All right. Twenty-two and a half.
How you gonna do "and a half"?
Twenty-two
and a half.
All right. Enjoy this party.
I like your style, man.
Stay on that boat, no matter what.
Adele, Nicks!
All right, guys, keep your earbuds in.
Like always, Adele,
you're my eyes in the sky.
Nicks, you're gonna show 'em
how we do it.
You got this?
Just watch.
Can you keep this
behind the bar for me?
- What can I get you?
- A cranberry and club soda.
Make that two.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Stay focused.
Really?
Xander Cage. Back in action.
Did I ever leave?
Oh.
Shit.
Spotted our clown.
Easier than expected. Drinks all around.
That's him.
What do you know?
It's douchebag hunting season.
My favorite.
It's a little early in the evening
to slay someone.
- Let me fix it.
- Oh, come on.
If Dance Dance Revolution
doesn't deserve a bullet,
I don't know who does.
Is this a party or a funeral?
It's a party!
Either way,
somebody's getting turnt up tonight!
I told you he was fun to have around.
At first, I thought Special Forces.
But your ink's all wrong.
CIA?
They would send in a drone,
bomb us to hell.
MI6?
You're not the kind of subtle they prefer.
You know, the men who come
to this island, they're on the run.
Hiding from the world.
But not you.
You're not here to hide.
You're looking for someone.
And who's to say
I haven't already found her?
Was that meant to scare me?
A little tremble would be nice.
Well,
considering you're one tremble away
from limping out of here...
...I'd say I'm close enough.
Does this mean you're not making me
breakfast in the morning?
I'd say you're a couple inches off.
Bit of a stalemate.
Not if you drop the gun.
I'm not the bad guy.
I don't believe in good guys.
Serena?
Who's your friend?
We just met.
But we were getting along
famously until somebody
decided to interrupt.
Stick to the path.
Here, honey.
There's a lot of
unmarked graves on the island.
I'll bet whoever sold you that shirt
is in one of them.
And how long do you intend to
push your luck?
Until I get what I came for.
Which is what exactly?
A damn,
A damn, strong drink.
So, let's be real and talk about
what we all really want.
I'm only here for that.
And in my mind,
you guys could walk away nicely.
Unless you want to
continue our foreplay.
Power like that doesn't belong
in anyone's hands.
Just improvising.
Mate, seriously? A grenade?
What is this?
Eastern Europe in the early '90s?
Next, he's gonna send you a fax.
So, you're willing to kill
just to keep that for yourself?
That's the wrong question to ask.
What's the right question?
"Are you willing to die for it?"
One grenade, three people.
I like the odds.
Two grenades, three people.
I'm loving these odds.
You ever bleed so much,
when you open your eyes,
all you see is red?
When you have fought war
on every continent...
Come on, X, just say the word.
Let me put both these assholes
out to pasture.
...you expect death.
Our bodies are such fragile things.
Come on. Let me shoot him.
Death sometimes just
sneaks up on you.
It's been a while
since I played hot potato.
I'm in this hospital bed.
I'm barely conscious. Delirious.
Drowning in my own blood.
And all I can hear myself think is,
"Today's the day."
"Today's the day you die."
I'm touched.
Can I have my jacket,
when you get a sec?
Then a man comes along,
tells me a story
about a drought in California.
About skateboards
and swimming pools.
About a man named Xander Cage.
Oh, shit. He's Triple-X.
I heard he was dead.
Is he?
We are all Triple-X.
We just have different agendas.
She wants to destroy it.
I'm gonna use it.
And I'll be damned if I'm gonna let you
take it back to the NSA.
I don't want a lover
I just need a friend
Now, it's a party.
Everybody, get down! Move! Move!
Shit's about to go down.
You ready to have some fun?
Turn the music off!
Stop it!
Everybody, hands up!
Now!
On the floor!
First person to move,
first person to die!
I moved.
I just moved again.
I'm still alive.
Shut up, "hero"!
All right.
Let's do this.
Don't move!
Okay, I actually have what you want.
Pandora's Box?
I got it right here.
But you're wrong, though.
You take it from me, and you die first.
Then Lieutenant Leningrad,
who thinks he's got your back.
Then the two Ivans by the door.
Moscow Mule by the bar.
And then Igor on the stairs.
See where we're going with this?
But none of that matters.
'Cause like I said,
if you take this from me, you die first.
I'll take it from you dead or alive.
And if you hold it too tight,
I cut your arm off.
Suit yourself.
Leningrad.
Hi, Ivan.
Other Ivan.
Whoo!
Ooh, bye-bye, Moscow Mule.
Igor. That's another one you owe me, X.
Read between the lines.
Tennyson!
Some back-up would be nice.
- Huh?
- Some back-up would be nice!
Come on, man!
X said stay on the boat.
That was before the goddamn
Russian invasion touched down, man!
X said stay on the boat.
You want to play?
That doesn't belong in anyone's hands.
You want it, come and get it.
Was that necessary?
It's what Gibbons would have wanted.
X!
X.
It happened again. Another satellite fell.
Us working as a team.
That's what Gibbons would've wanted.
You in?
An explosion inside
the Olympic Stadium rocks Moscow.
Seven workers are now confirmed dead,
with at least 25 others injured
in this senseless act of violence.
A source inside the Pentagon
says a rogue satellite
may have been used as a weapon.
Guess this means Pandora's Box
isn't exactly classified.
In a new video released
just moments ago,
an anonymous group
is claiming to have the ability
to use satellites as weapons.
They claim "that
the violation of civil liberties
"of all the citizens of the world
"is an atrocity that must be stopped."
Disable and
dismantle all the world's spy programs
within the next 24 hours,
or I'll do it for you,
one satellite at a time.
There are 30,000 satellites
orbiting the Earth at this moment.
I will drop one satellite every 24 hours
until my demands are met.
Eyewitnesses in Moscow...
Was this always part of
your mission, too?
Of course not.
We were a new T riple-X team
Gibbons created.
We discovered
a high-level intelligence officer
was trying to manipulate satellites.
And even before we could unmask him,
Gibbons was killed.
So, you knew they were
Triple-X all along.
I needed you to retain
a sense of objectivity.
I don't understand.
If I destroyed Pandora's Box,
what happened in Moscow?
If I'm right, which I am,
this box only ever had the ability
to control one satellite.
What does that mean?
It means
we've been chasing a prototype.
And these guys have the real one?
Yeah.
Serena played us for fools.
Betrayed us.
This isn't about Serena.
This is war. And either
we stop it today,
or we watch the world burn tomorrow.
- Can't lose focus on that.
- Yeah.
Where you been?
You stop off for the old rub-and-tug?
Your mom says hi.
Tracker on board? Nobody saw you?
- Nobody ever sees me, boss.
- Good.
Now, these suits control
every spy satellite in the sky.
But how often do these seven men
all sit in the same room together?
Almost never.
And if you needed
retinal scans,
cell phone data dumps,
biometrics of all
the superpowers in the world,
who would you target?
Oh, shit.
Who has that kind of power
to actually set that in motion?
Oh, you're pissing up
the wrong tree, Cage.
I came looking for you, remember?
Yo, asshole. We gonna have problems?
Oh, no problem. How was your trip?
I'm just doing the math.
Oh, yeah? What math?
Air velocity divided by distance.
So, when I stuff you down the toilet,
search and rescue will know where
to find you between China
and North Korea.
Keep talking shit, little man.
Hold that thought, G.I.Joe.
Wow.
Roll it back.
A little more.
More.
A little more. Stop.
Okay, when Xiang broke the window,
he's the only one that didn't flinch.
I need the President on the phone...
That's not gonna come off,
you know that, right?
I'll have to replace
the goddamn screen.
I've been saying the director of the CIA
has been trying
to destroy the world for years.
Okay, we have carte blanche to track
this son of a bitch down.
Do any of you know how to do it?
The same way Xiang and I found
Pandora's Box in New York.
Pandora's Box needs to
keep reconnecting itself
because the satellites orbit.
- Excuse me.
- Uh.
All we need to do is
track down the main signal,
and then we can approximate
its location within a 20-mile radius.
Of all the places
in the world to lay low,
this fruit loop chooses Detroit?
These blasts did take place in Moscow,
but they were felt around the world.
Good morning. As feared, the death toll
in the Moscow tragedy is rising.
In addition to the latest deaths...
Let me guess.
Everyone's jumping at the chance
to dismantle their spy programs.
No.
The world's too stupid to realize
that Moscow wasn't a bluff.
Okay, Triple-X,
you will base out of
an NSA safe house.
Becky will coordinate
earbud communications
and have the signal disruptor
on standby.
Nicks, when I crashed the boat up
on shore and saved your life...
Yeah, whatever, bro.
...do you think that counts
as crash 199 for me?
You know, officially?
Officially, you're deranged.
Cool.
We'll set up a triangulated
signal tracking system around the city.
And when
Becky locks in his exact location,
we make our move.
What about you?
How did you get roped into all this?
I tagged a skyscraper
and got a year in jail for it.
Jail?
- Seems excessive.
- Mmm-hmm.
The tag was 30 stories tall.
Two million hits on YouTube.
And I served only half the sentence.
Let me guess. Gibbons to the rescue.
Yup. He said a lion like me
doesn't belong in any kind of cage.
I got mine after I left the NSA.
What about that one on your wrist?
London.
2009. I climbed the Millennium Wheel.
Naked.
- Naked?
- Yeah.
High school.
Oh, no!
We all have our
embarrassing moments.
What about that sexy one?
This?
Phoenix out of the ashes.
Eighteen hours in a chair in Mexico.
I drank my bodyweight in tequila
to get through it.
It's the most important one, actually.
It's when I decided to change the world
instead of
rage against it.
We found him.
We found Pandora's Box.
Xander, do you copy?
We're here.
Okay, send Tennyson.
Uh, looks like East 404 Congress Street.
He's on the top floor.
I'm showing activity in Pandora's Box.
I can jam the signal,
but only for a few minutes, so hurry.
You've got to get there fast
and take this guy down.
Not if we find him first.
Whoa! Red light! Red light! Red light!
Whoo!
Did you know traffic signals
were invented by Big Oil
to waste fuel and drive up profits?
If I say yes, will you please
just slow down? Look out!
Wait.
Is this the part where you act
the basic bitch
and tell me you got your eye on me
and that you don't trust me?
- Welcome to the moment.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa
Everyone needs backup.
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Tennyson?
Gridlocked.
There it is.
If you run into trouble,
dial nine.
It's an old Gibbons fail-safe.
You crashed my party!
Stole my dance partner.
I'm gonna crash yours.
Have fun.
This ain't a party. This is a race.
What the hell you think you're doing?
Building a ramp.
Go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go!
- Hey! Out of the car! Get out!
- What are you doing?
Let's go!
Wow.
Shit. He's trying to reconnect it.
Guys, I can only
jam the signal for so long
before he chooses another satellite.
You have to hurry.
I have a plan.
Hold on!
"Hold on" ain't no goddamn plan!
No, no, no, no!
Hi.
You looking for someone?
That's 200!
Ha-ha! Come on.
No, no, no...
Xander, you got to get to the top floor.
He's trying to engage another satellite.
Hurry.
Fish in a barrel.
Forty-five U.S.P.
Twelve round mag.
Five left.
Three.
What the hell's going on out there?
Empty.
Adele, Xander's in.
Find the target, light him up.
Gibbons thought you'd be back.
To be the hero we needed.
You take the box to the NSA,
and we're right back to
where we started.
Wow.
This is touching.
Gibbons would be proud to
see you two working together.
I'm walking out of here, Xander.
You want to know a secret?
You forgot to put deodorant on?
I killed Gibbons because
he was a self-righteous prick.
Do you have a shot?
He thought
he had the right to police the world.
Adele,
do you have eyes on the target?
I'm switching to thermal.
I was never going to
stop downing satellites
no matter what happened.
You know why?
Because this world has turned...
Please, please, please
tell me you have a shot.
Damn it.
He's turned the heat up. I can't see shit.
X, can't see you guys.
Thermal's no good.
- Right?
- I've lost you in the heat.
You don't see
what's going on in this world?
Take it easy.
Huh?
So, what are you gonna do about it?
Easy.
X, keep Chatty Cathy talking.
I still don't have a shot.
We made it that way.
People like Gibbons and
the two of you. And me.
We made it that way. I mean, come on.
What's the point of getting up
in the morning
if you're not gonna
reboot the world, right?
Okay. Easy.
There's a war out there.
We're at war for our survival,
you don't see it?
Millions of people
have died for nothing...
It's their right.
Read between the lines.
Isn't it right?
I'm gonna be honest with you.
What's been bugging me
this whole time
is you've got something
stuck in between your teeth.
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm serious.
What the hell's wrong with you?
Right there.
Ahh!
Nice shot.
Was there ever a doubt?
Uh, yeah, I confess, I had my doubts.
That's for talking shit
about my friend, Gibbons.
Xiang! Get on your knees!
On your knees!
Hands! Hands!
On your knees, now.
Just in time.
Watch out, Cage. Keep this up,
people might mistake you
for one of the good guys.
Hey, suit.
You got what you wanted.
We both know he's not the bad guy.
And who do we blame for Moscow?
Better a living terrorist
than a dead company man.
You see what I'm saying?
Let's go.
Back on the plane.
I want wheels up in 20.
Let's go, boys.
We recovered Pandora's Box.
They're gonna send an extraction team
to pick you guys up.
But they're taking Xiang.
Oh, and, Serena,
if you don't hear from me,
remember, dial nine.
X takes care of its own.
You gave it back to Marke, didn't you?
Nice place. Spacious. Expensive.
Shut up.
Thank you, sir.
Yes, minimal casualties.
Triple-X performed
beyond any
reasonable measure of expectation.
Let me guess.
That was my invite to the Oval Office.
As of 10 minutes ago,
the Triple-X program
was officially shuttered.
All active agents are to be
erased from record
and considered enemies of the state.
It's just never a good idea
to point a gun at me.
Hey, are NSA extraction teams
normally armed like
they're invading Fallujah?
No, generally not.
Watch the boys.
Shit.
Oh, God, it's happening, isn't it?
They're gonna start
shooting at us, aren't they?
- Come on!
- Clear out, let's go!
It's showtime.
I guess we're on
the same team now.
Give me one.
You know me. Wind me up,
point me in the right direction.
Come on, let's go!
This shit is getting real, isn't it?
Is this what happens
when shit gets real?
What do we do?
Just be where the bullets aren't.
Sadly, the terrorist activated
Pandora's Box
one last time before we could stop him.
You and your entire team were lost
in the blast along with the device itself.
If the world thinks
Pandora's Box is gone,
then they won't know
we're using it to spy on them.
You're just another tyrant.
No. Patriot.
Let me educate you on the difference.
Xander!
They say
it's the last great adventure, Cage.
Be sure and send a postcard.
- Engines hot!
- Let's go!
Xander!
Xander Cage!
- Go, go!
- Everybody, fan out!
Find cover! Move!
Get behind there!
- There, take cover! Okay, okay.
- Get behind there!
What a rush.
Damn, Becky, that's some body armor.
Hey. I told you you got no manners.
Did your mother ever teach you
how to zip up your pants?
Shh...
Well?
Serena.
We're a bit busy now!
Marke's got Pandora's Box.
She's gonna drop a satellite
on top of you.
She's gonna drop a satellite on us!
Not if I jam the signal!
I need a power source!
Go!
Over there? By myself?
Cover me!
Fan out!
Go, go!
Hurry up, over there!
I go low.
I'll go high.
See if I can't find G.I.Joe.
Are you getting this interference?
Shit.
Take 'em out, now!
Everyone needs backup, right?
Yeah, I guess.
Let's do this.
Nicks!
- I've got a plan!
- No!
No, no, no!
Listen! From now on,
I make the plans, you execute!
Ow!
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God, this is fucking awesome!
What's wrong, hotshot?
No witty comeback?
I just finally figured out
that math problem.
It's gonna take two flushes.
Go, go, go!
Oh, shit. Way too many.
Let's get out of here.
Get back! Come on!
Oh, shit!
Oh, my, God, I'm gonna die.
Move!
Push forward!
This is all we've got.
Pin 'em! Pin 'em down!
Damn! I'm out of bullets. You got any?
No. Nothing.
I'm empty.
- We go on three.
- Okay.
Wassup?
Rock, paper, scissor, grenade launcher.
Darius Stone.
Triple-X since 2005.
Thanks for the assist.
X takes care of its own.
You got to be kidding.
We failed.
Xander, Marke activated
the satellite and it's headed right for us.
I'm gonna have to
take it out kamikaze style.
Don't do it. It's suicide.
Nobody could survive that fall.
Tell Nicks to have that camera ready.
Low-orbit freefall,
no chute and big fireworks.
They say it's the last great adventure.
Be sure to send a postcard.
I live for this shit.
Shit.
Nicks,
I hope you got that on camera!
If it ain't on video, it didn't happen!
Oh, yeah.
Hall of Fame shit right here, bro.
You know I could've done that, right?
- Bullshit.
- Shut up.
What happened to Marke?
The ground broke her fall.
Still don't believe in good guys?
It's okay if you're a little bad.
How bad?
Now, that right there,
that was a hell of an entrance.
That's a hell of a car.
Yeah. Gibbons told me
to keep an eye on it.
He said I'd know why
when I need to know why.
Now I know why.
It's exactly the way I left it.
I took it on a date or two.
X takes care of its own.
That's why I figured you'd come through.
To get a chance to work with
the legendary Xander Cage?
Where do I sign up?
You know, you done pissed on
the wrong damn picnic.
The whole world
gonna be looking for us.
I wouldn't have it any other way.
Oh, happy day
When Jesus washed
He washed our sins away
Oh, happy day
I'm talking about a happy day
He taught me how
To watch
Fight and pray
Praise the Lord
To fight and pray
Fight and pray
And live rejoicing
Oh, yeah
Every, every day
Every day
Oh, happy day
I'm talking about the sweet Lord
We thought we'd end
with Augustus' favorite song.
Wow, that's an impressive trick.
What?
Think you're the only one
who knows how to play dead?
Red roses too
Gotcha.
I see them bloom...
This is some pretty surreal shit,
being at your own funeral.
And I think to myself
I love that song.
What a wonderful world
And it could be a wonderful world,
if we just stopped doing bad shit to it.
If you wanted me out of retirement,
you could've just asked me.
You always responded to
less subtle motivation.
Now what?
You keep being the rebel
the world doesn't know it needs.
Watch the watchers.
Fight the enemy within.
Damn, that's so complicated.
Really?
Let me simplify it for you.
Kick some ass.
Get the girl.
And try to look dope
while you're doing it.
You can do "dope," can't you?
Sure you can.
Junior, let's bounce!
I'll see you later, X.
I can definitely make that work.
Let's do this.
You got me.
Gotcha.
I'm not a soldier, I'm a baller.
I'll see you later, X.
Sure you can.
Bye-bye.